Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=The Maid=
=الخادمة=
=Episode 19=
=الحلقة 19=
Father,
أب،
don't you recognize me now?
هل لم تتعرف علي الآن؟
You...
أنت...
That day, my mother
في ذلك اليوم، أمي
was beaten by you until she miscarried.
لقد تعرضت للضرب من قبلك حتى أجهضت.
I was drugged mute.
لقد تم تخديري حتى أصبحت أخرس.
For you,
لك،
my mother's life and mine
حياة أمي وحياتي
were even less valuable
كانت أقل قيمة
than your trivial amusements.
من تسلية تافهة.
(Who's your mother?)
(من هي أمك؟)
Qin Xiaoniang.
تشين شياو يانغ.
That female physician?
تلك الطبيبة؟
Xiaoniang's carrying a child
شياونيانغ تحمل طفلاً
in her womb.
في رحمها.
Madam Su ordered her beaten to death.
أمرت السيدة سو بضربها حتى الموت.
Please save her.
من فضلك انقذها.
That countryside woman
تلك المرأة الريفية
is lucky to die
من حسن حظه أن يموت
under my roof.
تحت سقفي.
Get lost.
اغرب عن وجهي.
Stop ruining my mood.
توقف عن تدمير مزاجي.
You're Yuqing?
أنت يو تشينغ؟
My lord, this isn't your first brush
سيدي، هذه ليست أول فرشاة لك
with death, huh?
مع الموت، هاه؟
If my mother hadn't saved you
لو لم تنقذك أمي
from that cliff back then,
من ذلك المنحدر في ذلك الوقت،
she wouldn't get raped by you.
لن يتم اغتصابها من قبلك.
She'd never have entered the Duke's Mansion.
لم تكن لتدخل قصر الدوق أبدًا.
She'd still be alive!
إنها لا تزال على قيد الحياة!
You
أنت
deserved death long ago.
استحق الموت منذ زمن طويل.
Qing.
تشينغ.
Please!
لو سمحت!
Save me!
أنقذني!
I'll make it up to you!
سأعوضك عن ذلك!
My lord,
سيدي،
farewell.
وداع.
(Mother,)
(الأم،)
(I've finally made the culprit atone for his sins.)
(لقد جعلت الجاني أخيرا يكفر عن خطاياه.)
Thank you for your help.
شكرا لك على مساعدتك.
No need for thanks.
لا حاجة للشكر.
Without you,
بدونك،
I couldn't have avenged my husband.
لم أستطع الانتقام لزوجي.
That day, when you exposed
في ذلك اليوم، عندما تعرضت
the Duchess's crime
جريمة الدوقة
in the worship hall,
في قاعة العبادة،
you gave me hope.
لقد أعطيتني الأمل.
The demoness has appeared.
لقد ظهرت الشيطانة.
Chaos descends.
الفوضى تنزل.
You planted
لقد زرعت
these words
هذه الكلمات
on Madam Su's corpse
على جثة السيدة سو
and in the Duke's
وفي الدوق
arrogant schemes.
مخططات متغطرسة.
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
Could you tell me
هل يمكنك أن تخبرني
the way to Meixiang House?
الطريق إلى منزل ميكسيانج؟
That way.
بهذه الطريقة.
Which way?
أي طريق؟
That way?
بهذه الطريقة؟
There.
هناك.
(The demoness has appeared) That way?
(ظهرت الشيطانة) بهذه الطريقة؟
(Chaos descends) I said that way!
(تنزل الفوضى) قلت ذلك بهذه الطريقة!
You mean left?
هل تقصد اليسار؟
It's over.
انتهى.
What
ماذا
will you do now?
ماذا ستفعل الان؟
I will take monastic vows.
سأتخذ عهودًا رهبانية.
A life of devotion
حياة من التفاني
amidst Buddha statues.
وسط تماثيل بوذا.
Sounds rather desolate.
يبدو مهجورا إلى حد ما.
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
These past years,
في السنوات الماضية،
I've never felt
لم أشعر أبدا
such relief until now.
مثل هذا الراحة حتى الآن.
Though my husband
على الرغم من أن زوجي
rests beneath the earth,
تقع تحت الأرض،
he can finally rest in peace.
وأخيرًا يمكنه أن يستريح بسلام.
That brings me peace.
وهذا يجلب لي السلام.
And you?
وأنت؟
Me?
أنا؟
The storm on my path
العاصفة في طريقي
has yet to subside.
لم تهدأ بعد.
Take care.
يعتني.
Wait.
انتظر.
This can't shield me from storms,
هذا لا يمكن أن يحميني من العواصف،
but it may warm you against the chill.
لكنها قد تدفئك من البرد.
I remember
انا اتذكر
there were many figures in it.
وكان فيه العديد من الشخصيات.
Poorly rendered ones.
تلك التي تم تقديمها بشكل سيئ.
So I painted over them.
لذلك قمت بالرسم فوقهم.
Might you
هل يمكنك
offer some advice?
هل تقدم بعض النصائح؟
Still refusing to be honest?
هل لا تزال ترفض أن تكون صادقا؟
Is this your true purpose
هل هذا هو هدفك الحقيقي؟
for approaching me?
لتقترب مني؟
You understand me best.
أنت تفهمني بشكل أفضل.
My weaknesses,
نقاط ضعفي،
pain,
ألم،
and desire
والرغبة
are all in your hands.
كلها بين يديك.
I originally wanted to wield you as a sword.
لقد أردت في الأصل أن أستخدمك كالسيف.
But in fact,
ولكن في الواقع،
you are the one holding the sword.
أنت من يحمل السيف.
How do you wish to deal with me?
كيف تريد أن تتعامل معي؟
Deal with?
التعامل مع؟
With all your schemes,
مع كل مخططاتك،
you've finally made me fall for you.
لقد جعلتني أقع في حبك أخيرًا.
I only want to hear the truth.
أريد فقط أن أسمع الحقيقة.
Slow down, Zhao.
أبطئ يا تشاو.
Be careful, Zhao.
كن حذرا، تشاو.
Don't fall down.
لا تسقط.
Isn't you perfectly aware
هل أنت على علم تام بذلك؟
of who I really am?
من أنا حقا؟
Zhao regards Shen Yuanjin as his birth mother.
يعتبر تشاو شين يوانجين بمثابة والدته الحقيقية.
I will never allow
لن اسمح ابدا
Zhao to be harmed by anyone.
تشاو لا يتعرض للأذى من قبل أي شخص.
Ye Xiyan,
يي شيان,
I don't care what you plan to do.
لا يهمني ما تخطط للقيام به.
Stop this at once.
أوقف هذا الأمر فورًا.
The masters on the mountain are extraordinary.
الأساتذة على الجبل غير عاديين.
(Pei Zhao, Heir of the Prince Regent) Master Lin has peerless spear skills.
(بي تشاو، وريث الأمير الوصي) يتمتع السيد لين بمهارات رمح لا مثيل لها.
Master Zhou wields sabers masterfully.
المعلم تشو يستخدم السيوف بمهارة.
And...
و...
Mother,
الأم،
why are you ignoring me again?
لماذا تتجاهلني مرة أخرى؟
What I miss most
ما أفتقده أكثر
is still you.
هل مازلت أنت؟
You indulge me in everything.
أنت تدعينني في كل شيء.
The masters never do.
السادة لا يفعلون ذلك أبدًا.
Zhao,
تشاو،
I've raised you for three years.
لقد ربيتك لمدة ثلاث سنوات.
Now it's time for you to repay this kindness.
والآن حان الوقت لرد هذا اللطف.
Master Zhao,
السيد تشاو،
His Highness seeks you.
سموه يبحث عنك.
Are you insane?
هل انت مجنون؟
His Highness cares most about Zhao.
صاحب السمو يهتم بتشاو أكثر من أي شيء آخر.
If he discovers you're using Zhao,
إذا اكتشف أنك تستخدم تشاو،
he won't let you off easily.
لن يتركك بسهولة.
Yes, I'm insane.
نعم أنا مجنونة.
She caused both my mother and father's deaths.
لقد كانت سببا في وفاة أمي وأبي.
The Western Army isn't under the Duke's control.
الجيش الغربي ليس تحت سيطرة الدوق.
And the Empress Dowager refuses to see me.
والإمبراطورة الأرملة ترفض رؤيتي.
If I don't act soon,
إذا لم أتصرف قريبا،
I'll be the next to die.
سأكون التالي للموت.
So you'd drag
لذلك عليك أن تسحب
Zhao into this conflict?
تشاو في هذا الصراع؟
We've worked hard to raise Zhao.
لقد عملنا بجد لتربية تشاو.
Do you think this doesn't pain me?
هل تعتقد أن هذا لا يؤلمني؟
Changyi.
تشانغي.
This is my only option left.
هذا هو خياري الوحيد المتبقي.
I would never harm Zhao.
لن أؤذي تشاو أبدًا.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
we three weren't a true family,
نحن الثلاثة لم نكن عائلة حقيقية،
yet bound tighter than any kin.
ومع ذلك، فهو مرتبط بشكل أقوى من أي قريب.
Wasn't that good enough?
ألم يكن هذا جيدا بما فيه الكفاية؟
Don't you wish to return to those days?
ألا ترغب بالعودة إلى تلك الأيام؟
What are you trying to do?
ماذا تحاول أن تفعل؟
Abdication and yielding to worthier candidates.
التنازل والاستسلام للمرشحين الأكثر جدارة.
Qing,
تشينغ،
you've won.
لقد فزت.
All affairs of the Prince Regent's Mansion
جميع شؤون قصر الأمير ريجنت
shall be managed by you.
سيتم إدارتها من قبلك.
I'll return Zhao
سأعود تشاو
to you too.
لك أيضا.
His Highness hasn't punished you.
لم يعاقبك سموه.
Why go to such lengths?
لماذا نذهب إلى هذه الأطوال؟
I was wrong in the past.
لقد كنت مخطئا في الماضي.
For the rest of my life,
لبقية حياتي،
I'll chant scriptures before Buddha,
سأرتّل الآيات أمام بوذا،
atoning to you and Qin Xiaoniang.
التكفير لك و تشين Xiaoniang.
I only hope
انا فقط اتمنى
you'll consider how I treated Zhao as my own,
ستفكر في كيفية تعاملي مع تشاو كأنه ابني،
raising him with care,
تربيته بعناية،
and forgive me.
وسامحني.
This is the swaddling clothes Zhao wore
هذه هي الملابس التي كان يرتديها تشاو
when first brought back.
عندما تم اعادته للمرة الاولى.
Such a tiny infant,
مثل هذا الطفل الصغير،
with feeble cries,
مع صرخات ضعيفة،
like a little kitten.
مثل قطة صغيرة.
At Zhao's first birthday,
في عيد ميلاد تشاو الأول،
he grabbed this wooden sword.
أمسك بهذا السيف الخشبي.
When Zhao first learned Luban locks,
عندما تعلم تشاو أقفال لوبان لأول مرة،
he couldn't open them.
لم يتمكن من فتحها.
So he threw them angrily on the floor
فألقاهم على الأرض غاضباً
and then picked them up,
ثم التقطتهم،
trying learning slowly.
محاولة التعلم ببطء.
I have no interest in raising another's child.
ليس لدي أي اهتمام بتربية طفل شخص آخر.
I know you hate me.
أعلم أنك تكرهني.
But Zhao has always seen me as his mother.
لكن تشاو كان ينظر إلي دائمًا كأمه.
If you kill me,
إذا قتلتني
how will he view you
كيف سوف ينظر إليك
when he learns of it?
عندما يعلم بذلك؟
You should cultivate virtue.
ينبغي عليك أن تزرع الفضيلة.
Refrain from meddling in worldly matters.
امتنع عن التدخل في أمور الدنيا.
Hit you.
ضربك.
Who told you
من قال لك
to bring her steamed buns and pickles daily?
هل تحضر لها الكعك المطهو ​​على البخار والمخللات يوميًا؟
I'll hit you.
سأضربك.
I'll kill you!
سأقتلك!
Stop!
قف!
You villain!
أيها الشرير!
It was you!
لقد كنت أنت!
You harmed my mother!
لقد أذيت أمي!
I'll hit you!
سأضربك!
(Shen Yuanjin,)
(شين يوانجين،)
(how dare you raise Zhao to be so spoiled?)
(كيف تجرؤ على تربية تشاو ليكون مدللًا إلى هذا الحد؟)
How dare you harm me?
كيف تجرؤ على أذيتي؟
You can treat others this way,
يمكنك التعامل مع الآخرين بهذه الطريقة،
and I'll treat you the same.
وسأعاملك بالمثل.
My father is the Prince Regent!
والدي هو الأمير الوصي!
I'll have him kill you!
سأجعله يقتلك!
Prince Regent, huh?
الأمير الوصي، هاه؟
Fine.
بخير.
Let me show you
دعني أريك
what the Prince Regent can do.
ماذا يستطيع الأمير الوصي أن يفعل؟
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
♪I once fell into deep love♪
???لقد وقعت في الحب العميق ذات مرة؟؟؟
♪Caught in a drama of love and hate♪
???محاصر في دراما الحب والكراهية؟؟؟
♪Trapped in self-made cages♪
???محبوسين في أقفاص من صنع أيديهم؟؟؟
♪To whom should I direct my questions♪
???إلى من أوجه أسئلتي؟؟؟
♪Heal my wounds from past dreams♪
???أشفي جروحي من أحلام الماضي؟؟؟
♪Fate bestowed me both joy and pain♪
"هل منحني القدر الفرح والألم؟"
♪Left me a kiss of love and hate♪
???تركت لي قبلة من الحب والكراهية؟؟؟
♪Who will unravel my dreams so deep♪
من سيكشف أحلامي العميقة؟
♪Who will save me from this lonely place♪
من سينقذني من هذا المكان الوحيد؟؟؟
♪Who will give me back my lonely grace♪
من سيعيد لي نعمتي الوحيدة؟
♪I dare not ask the infatuated ones♪
???لا أجرؤ على سؤال المعجبات؟؟؟
♪As the moonlight thickens♪
???مع ازدياد كثافة ضوء القمر؟؟؟
♪What I await♪
???ماذا أنتظر؟؟؟
♪Which heartless soul♪
???أية روح بلا قلب؟؟؟
♪Love departs, hatred persists♪
???الحب يرحل والكراهية تبقى؟؟؟
♪I woke too soon to bygone bonds♪
???لقد استيقظت مبكرًا جدًا على الروابط القديمة؟؟؟
♪Forgetting the lost one in old dreams♪
???نسيان المفقود في الأحلام القديمة؟؟؟
♪No longer waiting for estranged souls♪
???لم نعد ننتظر النفوس المنفصلة؟؟؟
♪Memories flow in the deep night♪
???تتدفق الذكريات في الليل العميق؟؟؟
♪Illuminating lonely spirits♪
???إضاءة الأرواح الوحيدة؟؟؟
♪Become an ordinary mortal♪
???أصبح إنسانًا عاديًا؟؟؟
♪Next spring will open heart's doors♪
"هل الربيع القادم سيفتح أبواب القلب؟"
♪Not seeking a specific beloved♪
???لا تبحث عن حبيب محدد؟؟؟
♪Gracefully embracing affections♪
???احتضان العواطف بلطف؟؟؟